Guide to the Mandy Carter Papers, 1970-2013 RL.00195
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Gigs and Events Series, 1979-2013, 108 boxes
  - NC NOW State Board Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Feb. 8 (Box 144)
  - Charlotte Forum on PK's, Charlotte, N.C., 1998 Feb. 9 (Box 144)
  - National Black Lesbian and Gay Conference, Washington, D.C., 1998 Feb. 12-15, 2 folders (Box 145)
  - UF LGBSU, University of Florida, Jacksonville, Fla., 1998 Feb. 13 (Box 145)
  - Warren Wilson College, Swannanoa, N.C., 1998 Feb. 16 (Box 145)
  - Mexico, 1998 Feb. 17-22 (Box 145)
  - DOJ Pride Program, 1998 Feb. 19 (Box 145)
  - NOW Summit, Washington, D.C., 1998 Feb. 20-22 (Box 145)
  - Campus Women's Leadership Conference, North Carolina State University, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Feb. 21 (Box 145)
  - ILGHRC Conference, New York, N.Y., 1998 Mar. 3 (Box 145)
  - Outfront, Minneapolis, Minn., 1998 Mar. 5-8 (Box 145)
  - EPF Meeting, 1998 Mar. 11 (Box 145)
  - NGLTF Public Policy Round Table, Washington, D.C., 1998 Mar. 12-13 (Box 145)
  - Passages, 1998 Mar. 14 (Box 146)
  - Spectrum Awards, Orlando, Fla., 1998 Mar. 15 (Box 146)
  - NC NOW PAC Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Mar. 28 (Box 146)
  - NC NOW State Board Meeting, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1998 Mar. 29 (Box 146)
  - Gay Lesbian Bisexual Student Association, UNC-Greensboro, Greensboro, N.C., 1998 Apr. 2 (Box 146)
  - Victory Foundation Advanced Training, San Francisco, Calif., 1998 Apr. 2-5 (Box 146)
  - East Tennessee State University, Johnson City, Tenn., 1998 Apr. 6-7 (Box 146)
  - University of Rhode Island, Kingston, R.I., 1998 Apr. 9-10 (Box 146)
  - New College, Sarasota, Fla., 1998 Apr. 16-17 (Box 146)
  - Durham Rape Crisis Center, Take Back the Night Speech, Durham, N.C., 1998 Apr. 18 (Box 146)
  - PRYSM, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Apr. 24-26 (Box 146)
  - SC Pride, Myrtle Beach, S.C., 1998 Apr. 30-1998 May 3 (Box 146)
  - Athena Project, St. Cloud State University, St. Cloud, Minn., 1998 May 6-10, 2 folders (Box 146)
  - DNC Gay Lesbian Caucus, Washington, D.C., 1998 May 7-9, 2 folders (Box 147)
  - "Threats to Democracy" PFAW Conference, Washington, D.C., 1998 May 15-18, 2 folders (Box 147)
  - DC Black Pride, Washington, D.C., 1998 May 21-24 (Box 147)
  - Federation of Black Prides, Washington, D.C., 1998 May 22 (Box 147)
  - Ypsilanti Meeting, 1998 May 29 (Box 147)
  - Triangle Foundation Dinner, Detroit, Mich., 1998 May 29-31 (Box 147)
  - Capital Pride Festival, Washington, D.C., 1998 May 30-June 7 (Box 148)
  - POCOF 3rd Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1998 June 8 (Box 148)
  - Black Radical Congress, Chicago, Ill., 1998 June 19-21 (Box 148)
  - Virginia Organizing Project, Roanoke, Va., 1998 June 19-21, 2 folders (Box 148)
  - National Women's Music Festival, Ball State University, Muncie, Ind., 1998 June 25-28 (Box 148)
  - NC NOW PAC Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 June 27 (Box 148)
  - Meeting with Elizabeth Birch, Washington, D.C., 1998 July 2 (Box 148)
  - Song Workshop at Highlander, New Market, Tenn., 1998 July 3 (Box 148)
  - Black Sexuality Summit, Washington, D.C., 1998 July 8-10 (Box 148)
  - NOW National Conference, Rochester, N.Y., 1998 July 10-12 (Box 148)
  - Women's Documentation Project Retreat, Upstate N.Y., 1998 July 17-19 (Box 148)
  - NABWMT, Fort Lauderdale, Fla., 1998 July 21-25 (Box 148)
  - NCLYN Summer Leadership Institute, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1998 July 28 (Box 148)
  - USSA Conference, Boulder, Colo., 1998 Aug. 1-4 (Box 148)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, 2nd Meeting, New York, N.Y., 1998 Aug. 5 (Box 148)
  - SONG POC Retreat, Mandy's Receipts, Little Rock, Ark., 1998 Aug. 13-17 (Box 148)
  - Kernersville UUA, Kernersville, N.C., 1998 Aug. 23 (Box 148)
  - NC NOW PAC, John Edwards Interview, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Aug. 26 (Box 148)
  - Forum Town Meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 1998 Aug. 27 (Box 148)
  - Meeting with Cedric, Washington, D.C., 1998 Aug. 28 (Box 148)
  - DC Black Pride Training, Washington, D.C., 1998 Aug. 29 (Box 149)
  - AFSC-LGBT Program Staff Gathering, Honolulu, Hi., 1998 Sept. 9-13, 2 folders (Box 149)
  - Dear Jesse, Durham, N.C., 1998 Sept. 15 (Box 149)
  - CBC Lesgislative Week, 1998 Sept. 16-19 (Box 149)
  - POCOF Events, Washington, D.C., 1998 Sept. 17 (Box 149)
  - AU-EPF Press Conference, Washington, D.C., 1998 Sept. 18 (Box 149)
  - Road to Victory, Washington, D.C., 1998 Sept. 18-19 (Box 149)
  - Down East Pride, Greenville, S.C., 1998 Sept. 19 (Box 149)
  - "Post-Pride" Discussion, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1998 Sept. 24 (Box 149)
  - BN/QN Showing, Durham, N.C., 1998 Sept. 25 (Box 149)
  - Unity Festival, Durham, N.C., 1998 Sept. 25-27 (Box 149)
  - MACT Dallas, 18th Anniversary Banquet, Dallas Pride Week, Dallas, Tex., 1998 Sept. 25-27 (Box 149)
  - NC NOW State Court, Raleigh, N.C., 1998 Oct. 3 (Box 150)
  - Bisexuals, Gays, Lesbians, and Allies for Diversity National Coming Out Day/Equality Begins at Home, 2nd Meeting, UNC-Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1998 Oct. 8 (Box 150)
  - Gill Foundation Video Shoot, Washington, D.C., 1998 Oct. 9 (Box 150)
  - Bridge Builders Conference, University of Maryland, College Park, Md., 1998 Oct. 10 (Box 150)
  - Minneapolis Training, 1998 Oct. 11 (Box 150)
  - National Coming Out Week Banquet, Minneapolis, Minn., 1998 Oct. 12 (Box 150)
  - University of Minnesota, Twin Cities National Coming Out Day, Minneapolis, Minn., 1998 Oct. 12, 2 folders (Box 150)
  - University of Minnesota, Morris/AHC Call, 2 classes, Morris, Minn., 1998 Oct. 10-13, 2 folders (Box 150)
  - Peace with Justice Week, Henderson, Ky., 1998 Oct. 15-18 (Box 150)
  - WRL 75th Anniversary, 1998 Oct. 16-18 (Box 150)
  - WRL Day Without Pentagon, Washington, D.C., 1998 Oct. 19 (Box 150)
  - Forum Town Meeting, New York, N.Y., 1998 Oct. 21-22 (Box 150)
  - UCC Conference, Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio, 1998 Oct. 26-27 (Box 151)
  - GLSEN Conference, Oakland, Calif., 1998 Oct. 30 (Box 151)
  - Black Town Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1998 Nov. 7 (Box 151)
  - Federation of Black Prides Conference Call, 1998 Nov. 8 (Box 151)
  - NGLTF/POCI, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1998 Nov. 11 (Box 151)
  - NGLTF Creating Change, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1998 Nov. 12-15 (Box 151)
  - Center for New Community, POC/Radical Right, Chicago, Ill., 1998 Nov. 13 (Box 151)
  - NCLYN Meeting MM 2000/NYAC, Durham, N.C., 1998 Nov. 17 (Box 152)
  - NCCU Brothers and Sisters, North Carolina Central University, Durham, N.C., 1998 Nov. 17 (Box 152)
  - Southeast Wage Gathering, Charleston, S.C., 1998 Nov. 21, 2 folders (Box 152)
  - World Council of Churches, Harare, Zimbabwe, 1998 Dec. 3-14, 9 folders (Box 153)
  - NOW/CIC Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1998 Dec. 5-6 (Box 152)
  - OPC Children's Youth Service, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1998 Dec. 17-18 (Box 152)
  - Lexington, Ky., 1998 Dec. 19 (Box 152)
  - GLSEN Meeting, New York, N.Y., 1998 Dec. 23 (Box 152)
  - Xmas Vacation, Schenectady, N.Y., 1998 Dec. 23-28 (Box 152)
  - Bannerman Fellowship, 1999 (Box 152)
  - Sabbatical, 1999, 2 folders (Box 152)
  - Firebrand Article, Kris Kleindienst, 1999 Jan. 11 (Box 152)
  - EBH-NC Meeting, Durham, N.C., 1999 Jan. 12 (Box 152)
  - National Religious Leadership Roundtable, Washington, D.C., 1999 Jan. 25-26, 3 folders (Box 152)
  - EPF Steering Committee Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1999 Jan. 27 (Box 154)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 1999 Jan. 28 (Box 154)
  - NGLTF National Policy Roundtable, Washington, D.C., 1999 Feb. 2-5 (Box 154)
  - AFSC Discussion Weekend, Phoenix, Ariz., 1999 Feb. 5-7 (Box 154)
  - Grassroots Alliance to End Poverty, Phoenix, Ariz., 1999 Feb. 5-7, 2 folders (Box 154)
  - NBLGLF Conference, Atlanta, Ga., 1999 Feb. 11-14, 2 folders (Box 154, 158)
  - Pride at Work Workshop, Washington, D.C., 1999 Feb. 12-13, 3 folders (Box 154-155)
  - BRC Meeting, UNC-Chapel Hill, Chapel Hill, N.C., 1999 Feb. 16 (Box 155)
  - SEC Conference, Duke University, Durham, N.C., 1999 Mar. 6 (Box 155)
  - "Shaking the Foundation," Stanford University, Palo Alto, Calif., 1999 Mar. 12-14 (Box 155)
  - Equality Begins at Home, Durham, N.C., 1999 Mar. 20 (Box 155)
  - NOW Meeting on MMOW, 1999 Mar. 26 (Box 155)
  - GLAXO-Welcome LGB Group, Reasearch Triangle Park, N.C., 1999 Apr. 2 (Box 155)
  - LOC Workshop, 1999 Apr. 6 (Box 155)
  - HRC Community Meeting, New York, N.Y., 1999 Apr. 14 (Box 155)
  - "Beyond Inclusion" Panel, New York, N.Y., 1999 Apr. 16 (Box 156)
  - Public Policy Speaker Series, New York, N.Y., 1999 Apr. 20 (Box 156)
  - NOW Lesbian Rights Summit, Washington, D.C., 1999 Apr. 23-25, 2 folders (Box 156)
  - David McReynolds Tribute, New York, N.Y., 1999 May 1 (Box 156)
  - Mautner LOC Program, Washington, D.C., 1999 May 8 (Box 156)
  - EPF Retreat, Harpers Ferry, W. Va., 1999 May 10-12 (Box 157)
  - AT&T League Conference, Minneapolis, Minn., 1999 May 14-16 (Box 157)
  - FEX Super Skills Weekend, Estes Park, Colo., 1999 May 20-22 (Box 157)
  - National Stonewall Democratic Federation, 1st Annual National Convention, Atlanta, Ga., 1999 May 21-23, 3 folders (Box 157)
  - DC Black Pride, Washington, D.C., 1999 May 29-30 (Box 157)
  - Northeast WOC Conference, Albany, N.Y., 1999 June 5-6 (Box 157)
  - NC Pride '99, Durham, N.C., 1999 June 12-13 (Box 158)
  - After Stonewall (cancelled), Durham, N.C., 1999 June 17 (Box 158)
  - Atlanta Pride, Atlanta, Ga., 1999 June 26-27 (Box 158)
  - SONG Birthday Event, Atlanta, Ga., 1999 June 26 (Box 158)
  - UCC National Summer Gathering, Providence, R.I., 1999 June 30 (Box 158)
  - Somerset, 1999 June 30 (Box 158)
  - Schenectady Trip, 1999 July 14-19, 2 folders (Box 158)
  - WRL NC Meeting, 1999 July 24-26 (Box 158)
  - San Francisco Trip, 1999 July 31-August 14 (Box 158)
  - POC-AHC Statement, Durham, N.C., 1999 Oct. 13 (Box 158)
  - Hate Crime Panel, San Francisco Public Library, San Francisco, Calif., 1999 Oct. 16 (Box 158)
  - NC Pride Board Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 1999 Oct. 30 (Box 158)
  - National Stonewall Democratic Retreat, Dallas, Tex., 1999 Nov. 5-7 (Box 159)
  - NSDF Board Meeting, Dallas, Tex., 1999 Nov. 6-7 (Box 159)
  - Glaxo Wellcome Inc. First Friday, RTP, N.C., 1999 Nov. 10-12 (Box 159)
  - AHC Town Meeting, Oakland, Calif., 1999 Nov. 12 (Box 159)
  - POC Gathering, Oakland, Calif., 1999 Nov. 12-13 (Box 159)
  - Firebrand Books Signing, San Francisco, Calif., 1999 Nov. 15 (Box 159)
  - Rebecca Helem Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1999 Dec. 4 (Box 159)
  - GNN Taping, MMOW, Fairfax, Va., 1999 Dec. 4 (Box 159)
  - MMOW DC Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1999 Dec. 5-6 (Box 159)
  - NSDF Interviews, Washington, D.C., 1999 Dec. 13 (Box 159)
  - Interview, FREE, 2000 Jan. 13-15 (Box 60)
  - MLK Weekend '99, NSDF, Washington, D.C., 2000 Jan. 16-17 (Box 159)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, National Religious Leadership Roundtable, Orange County, Calif., 2000 Jan. 31-Feb. 1 (Box 104)
  - Arrival Day File, 2000 Feb. 10 (Box 60)
  - Midwest LGBT College Conference, St. Cloud, Minn., 2000 Feb. 18-20 (Box 159)
  - Unity Dinner, St. Petersburg, Fla., 2000 Feb. 24 (Box 60)
  - LULAC Meeting, Tampa, Fla., 2000 Feb. 25 (Box 60)
  - Tampa Rally, Tampa, Fla., 2000 Mar. 2 (Box 60)
  - Statewide Bus Tour Rally in Tally, Tallahassee, Fla., 2000 Mar. 4-5 (Box 60)
  - March on Tallahassee, Tallahassee, Fla., 2000 Mar. 5-7, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Tally Rally, Tallahassee, Fla., 2000 Mar. 17 (Box 60)
  - Bread & Roses 25th Anniversary, SF Trip, San Francisco, Calif., 2000 Mar. 17-21 (Box 159)
  - Claiming the Rainbow, Leaven Gig, MSU, Lansing, Mich., 2000 Mar. 29-Apr. 1, 3 folders (Box 160)
  - Free Alachua Meeting, Gainesville, Fla., 2000 Apr. 20, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Audre Lorde Project, Keynote, 4th Annual Dinner Speaker, New York, N.Y., 2000 May 4 (Box 160)
  - Graduation Speech, Duke University, Terry Sanford School of Policy, Durham, N.C., 2000 May 13 (Box 160)
  - Meeting, 2000 May 16 (Box 60)
  - Save Dade Lambda Conference, Miami Beach, Fla., 2000 May 19-20, 3 folders (Box 60, 161)
  - St. Pete's Chamber of Commerce, 2000 May 24 (Box 60)
  - League of United Latin American Citizens (LULAC) Roast, Tampa, Fla., 2000 May 31 (Box 60)
  - NC Pride 2000, Durham, N.C., 2000 June 10, 20 folders (Box 161, 162)
  - 2nd Women's Meeting, Fort Lauderdale, Fla., 2000 June 12, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - USF One Florida Meeting, Tampa, Fla., 2000 June 13 (Box 60)
  - Pinellas NOW Press Event, St. Petersburg, Fla., 2000 June 14 (Box 60)
  - AFL-CIO Human Rights Conference, Miami Beach, Fla., 2000 June 15-17, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - HRC Meeting, Gainesville, Fla., 2000 June 16 or 20 (Box 162)
  - Site Visit for FREE Meeting, Orlando, Fla., 2000 June 21 (Box 61)
  - Pinellas Progressive Coalition, St. Petersburg, Fla., 2000 June 21 (Box 61)
  - Site Visit Orlando Meeting, Orlando, Fla., 2000 June 22 (Box 61)
  - Salon, 2000 June 23 (Box 162)
  - FREE Statewide Meeting, Orlando, Fla., 2000 June 24, 5 folders (Box 61)
  - NOW National Conference: Free to Be, Miami Beach, Fla., 2000 June 29-July 2, 2 folders (Box 162)
  - NOW National Conference Workshop, Miami Beach, Fla., 2000 July 1 (Box 163)
  - HRC Meeting, Lunch, Washington, D.C., 2000 July 5 (Box 163)
  - Elections 2000 Meeting Pinellas County, 2000 July 6 (Box 61)
  - Free Alachua Meeting, Gainesville, Fla., 2000 July 6, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Tampa Human Rights Committee Meeting, Tampa, Fla., 2000 July 10 (Box 61)
  - San Diego Pride 2000, San Diego, Calif., 2000 July 21-23, 2 folders (Box 163)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, National Religious Leadership Roundtable, Miami, Fla., 2000 July 23-25, 2 folders (Box 104)
  - Witness Our Welcome 2000, DeKalb, Ill., 2000 Aug. 3-6 (Box 163)
  - NSDF Conference 2000, Palm Springs, Calif., 2000 Aug, 10-12 (Box 163)
  - NAACP Training, Orlando, Fla., 2000 Aug. 26 (Box 61)
  - Lisa Kartik Me Meeting, Miami, Fla., 2000 Aug. 29 (Box 61)
  - FL NAACP Meeting, Miami, Fla., 2000 Aug. 30 (Box 61)
  - Meeting with Kirk, Miami, Fla., 2000 Aug. 31 (Box 61)
  - Arrive with Five Meeting, Miami, Fla., 2000 Aug. 31 (Box 61)
  - September 5th Primary Election, 2000 Sept. 5 (Box 66)
  - September 7th Call, 2000 Sept. 7 (Box 66)
  - AWS Tabling, Registration Week, Florida A&M University Registration Week, Tallahassee, Fla., 2000 Sept. 9 (Box 61, 66)
  - Wake Up Wednesday, 2000 Sept. 13 (Box 66)
  - African American Ministers Leadership Council (AAMLC) Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2000 Sept. 13-15, 3 folders (Box 61, 66)
  - Florida Vote/Equal Vote, 2000 Sept. 18-23 (Box 61)
  - Clearwater Site Visit, Clearwater, Fla., 2000 Sept. 19 (Box 61)
  - Apopka Site Visit, Apopka, Fla., 2000 Sept. 20 (Box 61)
  - PFAW Miami Meetings Site Visits, Miami, Fla., 2000 Sept. 21-24 (Box 61)
  - Khalid Meeting, 2000 Sept. 22 (Box 66)
  - Oscar Meeting, 2000 Sept. 22 (Box 66)
  - Adora Meeting, 2000 Sept. 22 (Box 66)
  - Haitian Meeting, 2000 Sept. 22 (Box 66)
  - Cocoa Site Visit, Cocoa, Fla., 2000 Sept. 23 (Box 61)
  - 57th Annual Florida NAACP State Convention, Jacksonville, Fla., 2000 Sept. 27-30, 3 folders (Box 61)
  - Orange County NAACP Meeting, Orlando, Fla., 2000 Oct. 2, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Orange County Voter's Coalition Meeting, Orlando, Fla., 2000 Oct. 5, 3 folders (Box 66)
  - Florida Vote Coordinating Meeting, Miami, Fla., 2000 Oct. 12, 3 folders (Box 66)
  - Arrive with Five Tour, Florida, 2000 Oct. 17-20 (Box 66)
  - Conference Call, 2000 Oct. 19 (Box 66)
  - Move to Miami from Gulfport, 2000 Oct. 19, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - FSA Board Meeting, Boca Raton, Fla., 2000 Oct. 20 (Box 66)
  - First Voters Seminar, Haitian Americans, Miami, Fla., 2000 Oct. 21 (Box 66)
  - In Person Meeting 2, 2000 Oct. 24 (Box 66)
  - Mobilization Meeting for Nov. 3, Miami, Fla., 2000 Oct. 25-27 (Box 66)
  - Prospect Donor Meeting, Miami, Fla., 2000 Oct. 26 (Box 67)
  - North Dade County Distribution List, 2000 Oct. 29 (Box 67)
  - Phonebanking Schedule Info for PFAW, Miami, Fla., 2000 Nov. 1-2 (Box 67)
  - Election Day, Miami, Fla., 2000 Nov. 7 (Box 67)
  - Creating Change 2000, Atlanta, Ga., 2000 Nov. 10-12, 5 folders (Box 163)
  - PR Presentation at Duke, Durham, N.C., 2000 Nov. 14 (Box 163)
  - NSDF Board Retreat, Fort Lauderdale, Fla., 2001 Jan. 6-7 (Box 164)
  - PFAW African American Ministers Leadership Council (AAMLC) Meeting, Fort Lauderdale, Fla., 2001 Jan. 10-12 (Box 67)
  - DNC Winter Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 Feb. 2-3, 3 folders (Box 164)
  - EPF Dinner Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2001 Feb. 3 (Box 164)
  - "Who Stole the Vote!?!", Durham, N.C., 2001 Feb. 10 (Box 164)
  - Meeting with Winnie Campbell, Washington, D.C., 2001 Feb. 14 (Box 164)
  - UNC-CH Teach-in, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2001 Mar. 1 (Box 164)
  - Stonewall Democrats Triangle, First Organizing Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2001 Mar. 19 (Box 164)
  - Mark's Draft DNC, 2001 Mar. 22 (Box 164)
  - Second Meeting With Winnie, Washington, D.C., 2001 Mar. 26 (Box 164)
  - Diversity Day, Gallaudet University, Washington, D.C., 2001 Mar. 27 (Box 165)
  - Jan Wright, 2001 Mar. 27 (Box 165)
  - Progressive Religious Partnership, Washington, D.C., 2001 Apr. 4-6 (Box 165)
  - BWFJ Banquet, Raleigh, N.C., 2001 Apr. 7 (Box 165)
  - Second Stonewall Triangle Meeting, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2001 Apr. 23 (Box 165)
  - Meeting with Ian, Equality NC, Durham, N.C., 2001 Apr. 25 (Box 165)
  - GLLC Dinner, Washington, D.C., 2001 Apr. 26 (Box 165)
  - Charlotte Pride, Charlotte, N.C., 2001 May 5 (Box 165)
  - DNC Southern Caucus Meeting, West Palm Beach, Fla., 2001 May 6 (Box 165)
  - DNC Voting Rights Institute, Riviera Beach, Fla., 2001 May 7, 2 folders (Box 165)
  - Triangle Stonewall Dems May Meeting, Potluck Picnic, Raleigh, N.C., 2001 May 20 (Box 165)
  - Northwestern University Rainbow Walk 2001, Evanston, Ill., 2001 May 20-25 (Box 165)
  - Weekend at Duffy's Housewarming, West Virginia, 2001 June 1-3 (Box 165)
  - Capital Pride Festival, Washington, D.C., 2001 June 4-10, 2 folders (Box 166)
  - Triangle Stonewall Dems, Durham, N.C., 2001 June 11 (Box 166)
  - SONG Training, Orlando, Fla., 2001 June 13-15 (Box 166)
  - NABWMT Convention 2001, New Orleans, La., 2001 June 14-21 (Box 166)
  - SF Travel Schedule, San Francisco, Calif., 2001 June 23-July 2 (Box 166)
  - CLOUT Conference Call, San Francisco, Calif., 2001 June 25 (Box 166)
  - NOA Gathering 5, Sonoma, Calif., 2001 June 28 (Box 166)
  - NCLR, 24th Anniversary Dinner, San Francisco, Calif., 2001 June 30, 2 folders (Box 166)
  - BRC Southern Conference, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2001 July 20-22 (Box 167)
  - Kopkind Colony 2001, Guilford, Vt., 2001 July 27-Aug. 5 (Box 167)
  - CLOUT Conference 2001, Black Mountain, N.C., 2001 Aug. 9-12 (Box 167)
  - NSD 3rd Annual Convention, Cleveland, Oh., 2001 Sept. 13-16 (Box 167)
  - DNC Fall Meeting 2001, Miami Beach, Fla., 2001. Sept. 13-16 (Box 167)
  - Robert, Josh, Nan FTM, Cambridge, Mass., 2001 Sept. 17 (Box 56)
  - Sue Hyde, North Carolina Gay & Lesbian Task Force, Cambridge, Mass., 2001 Sept. 17 (Box 56)
  - Beth Jacklin, Cambridge, Mass., 2001 Sept. 17 (Box 56)
  - FTMC Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Sept. 19 (Box 56)
  - Mary Robert Josh, Boston, Mass., 2001 Sept. 19 (Box 56)
  - Evan Wolfson, New York, N.Y., 2001 Sept. 20-21 (Box 56)
  - 2nd Trip to Boston, Travel Day, 2001 Sept. 21 (Box 56)
  - NC NOW State Conference, Fayetteville, N.C., 2001 Sept. 22 (Box 167)
  - 2nd Trip to Boston Work Day, Boston, Mass., 2001 Sept. 26 (Box 56)
  - 2nd Joint Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Sept. 27 (Box 56)
  - NC Pride Fest 2001, Durham/Raleigh, N.C., 2001 Sept. 27-Sept. 30, 2 folders (Box 167)
  - Out Equal Workplace Summit, Erlanger, Ky., 2001 Oct. 5-7, 3 folders (Box 56, 167)
  - 2 Day Travel Day to Beth's, 2001 Oct. 7-9 (Box 56)
  - Set up Office at Beth and Carl day, Dorchester, Mass., 2001 Oct. 10 (Box 56)
  - 3rd World Joint Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 11 (Box 56)
  - National Coming Out Day Program, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 11 (Box 56)
  - Field Trip to New Bedford Site Visit Fall River, New Bedford, Mass., 2001 Oct. 12-13 (Box 56)
  - Speak Out 2001 Training, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 14 (Box 56)
  - Meeting at Quad re: POC Contacts, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 16 (Box 56)
  - FTMC MEeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 17 (Box 56)
  - Meeting with Valerie, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 18 (Box 56)
  - Into Office Errands, 2001 Oct. 19 (Box 56)
  - Free Day/Dinner Meeting, Dorchester, Mass., 2001 Oct. 20-21 (Box 56)
  - Meeting with Evan and Tim, New York, N.Y., 2001 Oct. 22 (Box 57)
  - Meeting at LLDEF, New York, N.Y., 2001 Oct. 23 (Box 57)
  - FTMC Dance Committee Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 24 (Box 57)
  - 4th Joint Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 26 (Box 57)
  - Roundtrip Drive to Durham, Durham, N.C., 2001 Oct. 26-27 (Box 57)
  - Keith Boykin Sabrina Soujourner, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass., 2001 Oct. 28 (Box 57)
  - FTMF Hard Questions Training, Boston, Mass., 2001 Oct. 29 (Box 57)
  - Office Days, Boston, Mass., 2001 Nov. 5-9 (Box 57)
  - FTMC Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Nov. 7 (Box 57)
  - NGLTF Creating Change 2001, Milwaukee, Wis., 2001 Nov. 7-11 (Box 167)
  - Meeting with Rich Cowan, Boston, Mass., 2001 Nov. 8 (Box 57)
  - Office Days Chris Cobb Mtg., 2001 Nov. 12-13 (Box 57)
  - Northeast NOW Summit, Fairlee, Vt., 2001 Nov. 16-18, 3 folders (Box 57)
  - Office Day, Meeting with Beth, 2001 Nov. 19 (Box 57)
  - Meeting, Arnold Sapenter, 2001 Nov. 20 (Box 57)
  - Andre Davis, 2001 Nov. 19-20 (Box 57)
  - Thanksgiving Holiday, 2001 Nov. 21-25, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Office Day, Sylvia, Rhue Call, 2001 Nov. 26-27 (Box 57)
  - Official FTMC Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Nov. 28-29 (Box 57)
  - Office Day, 2001 Nov. 29-30 (Box 57)
  - Union United Methodist Church, Boston, Mass., 2001 Dec. 1-2 (Box 58)
  - Massachusetts NOW Conference, Boston, Mass., 2001 Dec. 2 (Box 58)
  - Meeting with Andrea Lee: Speaker Boston NOW, Boston, Mass., 2001 Dec. 3 (Box 58)
  - Checking Call with Evan, 2001 Dec. 3-4 (Box 58)
  - FTMC Meeting, 2001 Dec. 5 (Box 58)
  - Field Trip to Fall River, New Bedford, Mass., 2001 Dec. 6-7, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - 1st Annual MoCAA Awards Fun Drive, Boston, Mass., 2001 Dec. 8 (Box 58)
  - Meetings with Sue Hyde, Jenney Firestone, RCFM Monthly Meeting, 2001 Dec. 10 (Box 58)
  - Call with Mitzi UCC, 2001 Dec. 11 (Box 58)
  - Moving Day "RCFM Mailing--Done!", 2001 Dec. 13 (Box 58)
  - Four Proposals Freedom Out, 2001 Dec. 14 (Box 58)
  - Office Days, Dinner with Robyn Ochs, 2001 Dec. 17-18 (Box 58)
  - "Next Steps" Meeting, Boston, Mass., 2001 Dec. 19, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - "Next Steps" Meeting with Jennifer, Pack Up Office Day, 2001 Dec. 20 (Box 58)
  - Last Day in Office Day, Pack up, Drive to Schnectady, 2001 Dec. 24 (Box 58)
  - Check-In Call with Evan, 2001 Dec. 29-31 (Box 58)
  - Call with Evan, 2002 Jan. 2 (Box 58)
  - Call #2 with Evan, 2002 Jan. 3 (Box 58)
  - Office Day, Check in Call Evan, 2002 Jan. 4 (Box 58)
  - Office Day, Radio Interview, 2002 Jan. 7 (Box 58)
  - Calls with Jennifer Levi, Calls with Josh, 2002 Jan. 8 (Box 58)
  - Office Day, 2002 Jan. 9 (Box 58)
  - Office Day, 2002 Jan. 10 (Box 58)
  - Office Day Errands Day, 2002 Jan. 11 (Box 58)
  - Packing day, Drive Back to Boston, 2002 Jan. 12 (Box 58)
  - Set Up Office, RCFM Meeting, Conference Call with Evan, 2002 Jan. 14 (Box 58)
  - Office Day, 2002 Jan. 15 (Box 58)
  - FTMC Meeting, 2002 Jan. 16 (Box 58)
  - Office Day Film with Beth, 2002 Jan. 17 (Box 58)
  - Office Day, 2002 Jan. 18 (Box 58)
  - Fun Drive, Alice Max Run for 1/26 Supplies, 2002 Jan. 19 (Box 58)
  - Checkout of Oasis Move Into Roberts MCC Boston Service Office Day, 2002 Jan. 20 (Box 58)
  - Put Packets Together, Move Out day. Drive Day to Washington, D.C., 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 58)
  - Meeting with Kim UCGA, National NOW, Washington, D.C., 2002 Jan. 22 (Box 58)
  - Site Visit to MOCAA, Office Day, Boston, Mass., 2002 Jan. 23 (Box 58)
  - Lunch with Ken Reeves, Drive to NYC for Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2002 Jan. 24 (Box 58)
  - Funding Exchange Asot Mispat Fun Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2002 Jan. 25 (Box 168)
  - People of Color Freedom to Marry Organizing in Massachusetts, 2002 Jan. 26 (Box 58)